<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Notes on</title><link>https://forgetful.dev/notes/</link><description>Recent content in Notes on</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><atom:link href="https://forgetful.dev/notes/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Arpeggio</title><link>https://forgetful.dev/notes/Arpeggio/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://forgetful.dev/notes/Arpeggio/</guid><description> Definition # An arpeggio is a type of broken-chord in which the notes that compose a chord are individually sounded in a progressive rising or descending order. Arpeggios on keyboard instruments may be called rolled chords.
Arpeggios indicate a chord in which the notes are sounded individually. The word &amp;ldquo;arpeggio&amp;rdquo; comes from the Italian word &amp;ldquo;arpeggiare,&amp;rdquo; which means to play on a harp.
Go back</description></item><item><title>Atomic Notes</title><link>https://forgetful.dev/notes/Atomic-Notes/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://forgetful.dev/notes/Atomic-Notes/</guid><description>Atomic notes are single, self-contained notes that capture a single idea or piece of information. They are meant to be read and understood without needing to refer to anything more. They can be connected to another atomic note or idea in some way. By breaking down complex ideas into smaller, atomic notes, one can make their notes more organized and easier to review later.
Get Home</description></item><item><title>Chords (music)</title><link>https://forgetful.dev/notes/Chords/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://forgetful.dev/notes/Chords/</guid><description> Definition # A chord, in music, is any harmonic set of pitches/frequencies consisting of multiple notes (also called &amp;ldquo;pitches&amp;rdquo;) that are heard as if sounding simultaneously.
Go back</description></item><item><title>Continuous Care</title><link>https://forgetful.dev/notes/Continuous-Care/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://forgetful.dev/notes/Continuous-Care/</guid><description>Be the watchful caretaker of your ever growing plants and flowers. Grow your knowledge by forming new branches and connecting the dots. Write short structured notes articulating specific ideas and share them here. One note in your digital garden = one idea. Avoid creating or nourishing orphan notes. Anything not connected eventually needs to go. We must: refine our ideas, thread our thoughts, and keep notes [[content/notes/Atomic Notes|atomic]].
Taking raw notes is useless.</description></item><item><title>Micropolitan Statistical Area</title><link>https://forgetful.dev/notes/Micropolitan-Statistical-Area/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://forgetful.dev/notes/Micropolitan-Statistical-Area/</guid><description>Micropolitan Statistical Areas are labor market and statistical areas in the United States centered on an urban cluster with a population of at least 10,000 but fewer than 50,000 people.
The designation was created in 2003 by the Office of Management and Budget (OMB). Micropolitan areas include the county where the urban cluster is and adjacent counties linked by commuting ties. The OMB has identified 543 micropolitan areas in the United States.</description></item><item><title>MPV Player</title><link>https://forgetful.dev/notes/MPV/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://forgetful.dev/notes/MPV/</guid><description> mpv.conf # volume=50 profile=gpu-hq scale=ewa_lanczossharp cscale=ewa_lanczossharp video-sync=display-resample interpolation tscale=oversample</description></item><item><title>Sans-serif</title><link>https://forgetful.dev/notes/sans-serif/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://forgetful.dev/notes/sans-serif/</guid><description>In typography and lettering, a sans-serif, sans serif, gothic, or simply sans letterform is one that does not have extending features called &amp;ldquo;serifs&amp;rdquo; at the end of strokes. Sans-serif typefaces tend to have less stroke width variation than serif typefaces. They are often used to convey simplicity and modernity or minimalism.
Code # font-family: -apple-system, BlinkMacSystemFont, &amp;#34;Avenir Next&amp;#34;, Avenir, &amp;#34;Nimbus Sans L&amp;#34;, Roboto, Noto, &amp;#34;Segoe UI&amp;#34;, Arial, Helvetica, &amp;#34;Helvetica Neue&amp;#34;, sans-serif; Read more</description></item><item><title>Serif</title><link>https://forgetful.dev/notes/serif/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://forgetful.dev/notes/serif/</guid><description>In typography, a serif (/ˈsɛrɪf/) is a small line or stroke regularly attached to the end of a larger stroke in a letter or symbol within a particular font or family of fonts.
Code # font-family: Constantia, &amp;#34;Lucida Bright&amp;#34;, Lucidabright, &amp;#34;Lucida Serif&amp;#34;, Lucida, &amp;#34;DejaVu Serif&amp;#34;, &amp;#34;Bitstream Vera Serif&amp;#34;, &amp;#34;Liberation Serif&amp;#34;, Georgia, serif; Read more</description></item><item><title>Sweep Your Mind</title><link>https://forgetful.dev/notes/Sweep-Your-Mind/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://forgetful.dev/notes/Sweep-Your-Mind/</guid><description>These notes make it possible to offload a massive amount of information while demonstrating &amp;ldquo;perfect recall&amp;rdquo; when needed. The goal of a mind sweep is to identify everything that requires your attention or has the possibility of seeping into and affecting other parts of your life. These include things that are stealing your focus, not letting you get your work done properly, etc.
When you identify these things, you will realize that there are things in your head that you haven’t been doing anything about.</description></item></channel></rss>